<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xml:base="http://badcamp2011.dev"  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss">
<channel>
 <title>BADcamp 2011</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev</link>
 <description></description>
 <language>en</language>
<item>
 <title>It&#039;s All Happening</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/news/its-all-happening</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;**Getting to BADcamp/Parking**&lt;br /&gt;
There is no Cal Football game this year, so parking should be MUCH&lt;br /&gt;
easier than last year. By all means, take BART if you can - it&#039;s closer&lt;br /&gt;
than almost anywhere you can park and cheaper. See the map here:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics/directions&quot; title=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics/directions&quot;&gt;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics/directions&lt;/a&gt;. But if you are bringing&lt;br /&gt;
your car to BADcamp, grab a buddy and check out our handy map here:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&quot; title=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&quot;&gt;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Registration - Saturday &amp;amp; Sunday, 8:30am-9:30am**&lt;br /&gt;
Registration, as well as many of our sessions, will be in Dwinelle Plaza&lt;br /&gt;
on the Berkeley Campus. Yes, we have a map for that:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&quot; title=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&quot;&gt;http://2011.badcamp.net/logistics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Join us at 8:30 for coffee, vegan donuts, &amp;amp; bagels, and get your BADcamp&lt;br /&gt;
badge, schedule, and wi-fi access code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Parties**&lt;br /&gt;
The rumors are true, BADcamp does like to party. If you&#039;re only coming&lt;br /&gt;
to the camp, you&#039;re missing half the fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Saturday - An Evening of Drupal at Zellerbach Auditorium - 6pm*&lt;br /&gt;
This is going to be a night to remember. We sincerely hope you&#039;ll join&lt;br /&gt;
us in the beautiful Zellerbach Auditorium to mingle, enjoy the musical&lt;br /&gt;
stylings of DJ Batson and DJ Spinnerty, partake in FREE tacos,&lt;br /&gt;
flatbreads, nachos, and flautas for dinner, and have a drink or two on&lt;br /&gt;
BADcamp before the main program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We have three fantastic speakers from Drupal and beyond:&lt;br /&gt;
* Dries Buytaert, Creator of Drupal&lt;br /&gt;
* Jeff Robbins, Founder, Lullabot&lt;br /&gt;
* Danese Cooper, Open Source Strategist for the Bill &amp;amp; Melinda Gates&lt;br /&gt;
Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, we&#039;ll keep the party going at Zellerbach with DJs and Drinks&lt;br /&gt;
until 11:30pm before heading over to the Bear&#039;s Lair Pub on campus until&lt;br /&gt;
2am. All evening events are just a short stroll from the BADcamp basecamp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Get the map and full program details here:&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/sessions/evening-drupal-dine-drink-and-drupal&quot; title=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/sessions/evening-drupal-dine-drink-and-drupal&quot;&gt;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/sessions/evening-drupal-dine-drink-and-d...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Coder Lounge - Hotel Shattuck, 6th Floor**&lt;br /&gt;
The CHX Coder Lounge will be open from Friday at noon and through the&lt;br /&gt;
weekend. Coffee service will begin at 3:45pm and will be available 24&lt;br /&gt;
hours, as will the room itself. So when inspiration strikes at 3am,&lt;br /&gt;
we&#039;ve got you covered (and caffeinated).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coder Lounge will not be doing any registration so please pick up&lt;br /&gt;
your badge at one of the trainings, summits, pre-registration, or at&lt;br /&gt;
registration on Sat/Sun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;**Birds of a Feather - Signups Open Online**&lt;br /&gt;
BOF Room Signup is Open! &lt;a href=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/bofs&quot; title=&quot;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/bofs&quot;&gt;http://2011.badcamp.net/program/bofs&lt;/a&gt; We&#039;ll have&lt;br /&gt;
the traditional sign-up board at the event, but if you want to reserve a&lt;br /&gt;
room now, you can do so on the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, got all that? Great. Get some sleep, pack a hoodie (it&#039;s NorCal)&lt;br /&gt;
and your love of all things Drupally, and get ready to spend your&lt;br /&gt;
weekend with BADcamp. All 1450 of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;- Team BADcamp&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://badcamp2011.dev/news/its-all-happening#comments</comments>
 <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2011 00:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>badcamp</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">469 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Developer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/solar-mosaic/drupal-developer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/solar-mosaic&quot;&gt;Solar Mosaic&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solar Mosaic is a platform that anyone can use to create solar projects and finance them from their communities. Solar Mosaic connects people who want to go solar with the buildings that have the ideal roofs and space to go solar. Mosaics are works of art where many pieces come together to form a whole. With Solar Mosaics, many people come together to build community solar projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Position:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Solar Mosaic is looking for a Drupal development superhero with a passion for social change to help us build the worlds first community solar platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will work in a growing team of developers as we constantly improve our online platform, building features that allow communities to come together, build solar projects, track their impact and see their prosperity grow.  Working closely with our team members and our community, you will help create a vision for the future of our product.  The tools you help build will be used by communities around the world to build prosperity through clean energy.  You will be a super hero.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Skills/Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert Level Drupal Skills (Module Development, Themeing, Configuration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agile Project Management (we use Pivotal Tracker)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;LAMP Stack Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Performance Monitoring and Optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High Volume E-Commerce Site Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Member Data and Server Security&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management of Remote and Overseas Developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for Building a Community Solar Movement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Position is part-time to start with potential for full-time in the near future.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competitive salary with benefits and earned equity commensurate to experience.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email your resume and cover letter to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:theteam@solarmosaic.com&quot;&gt;theteam@solarmosaic.com&lt;/a&gt; with your name and the position in the subject line, like this ‘John Doe for Drupal Developer’&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://solarmosaic.com&quot;&gt;Check out our website to learn more about us.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 19:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>arthurcoulston</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">467 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Marketing Assistant</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/imagex-media/marketing-assistant</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/imagex-media&quot;&gt;ImageX Media&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you have a passion for marketing, an outgoing personality and experience in the web industry? This may be the job for you:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://imagexmedia.com/about&quot; title=&quot;http://imagexmedia.com/about&quot;&gt;http://imagexmedia.com/about&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 17:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>glennhilton</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">465 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Technical Support Engineer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/chapter-three/technical-support-engineer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/chapter-three&quot;&gt;Chapter Three&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chapter Three is looking to hire a Technical Support Engineer to work with our team in our San Francisco office and our customers nationwide.  We’re serious about providing fantastic support to our customers.  We’re looking for solid experience with Drupal and an ability to troubleshoot customer needs, advocate for the customer within our organization, and come up with outstanding solutions.  You’ll be working closely with our engineers and designers to find the best solutions possible for our customers.  Chapter Three is one of the top Drupal shops anywhere with an interesting variety of clients.  This is a great opportunity for the right person; if that is you, please get in touch!  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chapterthree.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;http://www.chapterthree.com/careers&quot;&gt;http://www.chapterthree.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 21:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>ehestenes</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">459 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Site Developer, Web Engineer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/nvelo/drupal-site-developer-web-engineer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/nvelo&quot;&gt;NVELO&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NVELO is a well-funded company, with lots of good talent and technology - but we need someone to &#039;own&#039; our internet presence, from corporate web site, to user-forums, software product delivery, ecommerce, etc. Good thing is that you get to start from scratch - no legacy junk to deal with - pick our ISP, pick our hardware/servers, pick our infrastructure (Drupal?), and off we go...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nvelo.com&quot; title=&quot;http://www.nvelo.com&quot;&gt;http://www.nvelo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, if you set up such a high-quality/low-maintenance infrastructure that you find yourself with &#039;extra time&#039;, then we&#039;ve got ton&#039;s of other areas that you can explore: software dev, apps engineering, etc. Its all about creating an environment where intelligent people can create and add value...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shoot me an email if you think this sounds interesting: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:kevin@nvelo.com&quot;&gt;kevin@nvelo.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kevin Silver&lt;br /&gt;
VP Business Development&lt;br /&gt;
NVELO, Inc.&lt;br /&gt;
5201 Great America Parkway&lt;br /&gt;
Santa Clara, CA 95126&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 19:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>kevin@nvelo.com</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">456 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>System Administrator</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/promet-source/system-administrator</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/promet-source&quot;&gt;Promet Source&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PrometSource.com - a Chicago based web and mobile application development company - is looking to hire a System Administrator. We build some of the more innovative Drupal websites and have great clients that are leaders in their communities and have extensive reach in the broad audience. We are looking to add an experienced System Administrator who wants to be a part of a fun, collaborative team of individuals where every one&#039;s voice is heard and all ideas are always considered. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The System Administrator is responsible for effective provisioning, installation/configuration, operation, and maintenance of systems hardware and software and related infrastructure. This individual participates in technical research and development to enable continuing innovation within the infrastructure. This individual ensures that system hardware, operating systems, software systems, and related procedures adhere to organizational values.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This individual will assist project teams with technical issues in the Initiation and Planning phases of our projects. These activities include the definition of needs, benefits, and technical strategy; research &amp;amp; development within the project life-cycle; technical analysis and design; and support of operations staff in executing, testing and rolling-out the solutions. Participation on projects is focused on smoothing the transition of projects from development to production by performing operations activities within the project life-cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System Administrator Engineering and Provisioning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Engineering of SA-related solutions for various project and operational needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Install new / rebuild existing servers and configure hardware, peripherals, services, settings, directories, storage, etc. in accordance with standards and project/operational requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3. Install and configure systems such as supports infrastructure applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4. Develop and maintain installation and configuration procedures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5. Contribute to and maintain system standards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6. Research and recommend innovative, and where possible automated, approaches for system administration tasks.  Identify approaches that leverage our resources and provide economies of scale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Operations and Support&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7. Perform daily system monitoring, verifying the integrity and availability of all hardware, server resources, systems and key processes, reviewing system and application logs, and verifying completion of scheduled jobs such as backups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;8. Perform regular security monitoring to identify any possible intrusions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9. Perform daily backup operations, ensuring all required file systems and system data are successfully backed up to the appropriate media, recovery tapes or disks are created, and media is recycled and sent off site as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10. Perform regular file archival and purge as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;11. Create, change, and delete user accounts per request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12. Provide other support per request from various staff members.  Investigate and troubleshoot issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;13. Repair and recover from hardware or software failures.  Coordinate and communicate with impacted parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maintenance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;14. Apply OS patches and upgrades on a regular basis, and upgrade administrative tools and utilities. Configure / add new services as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15. Upgrade and configure system software that supports infrastructure applications per project or operational needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;16. Maintain operational, configuration, or other procedures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;17. Perform periodic performance reporting to support capacity planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18. Perform ongoing performance tuning, hardware upgrades, and resource optimization as required.  Configure CPU, memory, and disk partitions as required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;19. Maintain data center environmental and monitoring equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KNOWLEDGE/SKILLS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Bachelor (4-year) degree, with a technical major, such as engineering or computer science.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. Two to four year’s system administration experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competitive pay and ability to work on fantastic clients in a laid back fun environment. The experience of working directly with friendly and supportive clients. Some of our past and current clients include sba.gov, sprint.com, large associations with major offices in DC area (can&#039;t mention them by name), startups, small business and lots of creative companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course we offer competitive compensation, full health care plan and profit sharing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Promet Source is an Open Source Web and Mobile web application development company. Promet has been building open source websites since 2003.  We are a very entrepreneurial company which seeks to continually redevelop its skill set. We are a flat organization which means everyone has a say and we encourage everyone to develop their interest. We love to work on social aspects of the web and mobile apps. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email resumes to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:jobs2@promethost.com&quot;&gt;jobs2@promethost.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 17:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>theabrown</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">454 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Developer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/promet-source/drupal-developer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/promet-source&quot;&gt;Promet Source&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PrometSource.com - a Chicago based web and mobile application development company - is looking to hire Drupal experts to its established team of Drupal professionals. We build some of the more innovative Drupal websites and have great clients that are leaders in their communities and have extensive reach in the broad audience. We are looking to add developers that have experience in building large and complex solutions and want to be a part of a fun, collaborative team of individuals where every one&#039;s voice is heard and all ideas are always considered. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for some seriously dedicated developers. If you love code, have a great understanding of the web and how scripting languages work you must apply. Read the list of technical skills we prefer you have familiarity with below. However, if you have a similar experience in another open source area great attitude, a burning desire to learn, proven technical acumen, and are creative enough to convince us,.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for someone who has:&lt;br /&gt;
Strong understanding of best practices in Drupal development.&lt;br /&gt;
Knowledge of many Drupal modules&lt;br /&gt;
HTML, CSS expertise&lt;br /&gt;
Ability to develop in PHP/MySQL&lt;br /&gt;
Knowledge and experience with API development&lt;br /&gt;
Proven Custom module development&lt;br /&gt;
Understands Integration concepts (restful services, API development, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;
Knowledge of PHP and MySQL development techniques: using svn or GIT for code checkouts, version control, and deployment techniques.&lt;br /&gt;
The ability to interact with clients and help them to understand Drupal. This includes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploring ideas for how to use the platform, and explaining what various modules do.&lt;br /&gt;
Collecting requirements and helping people craft their strategy for how to use their web sites.&lt;br /&gt;
Provide expertise on the best practices in Drupal and technical strategy direction for our clients to be able to meet their business goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonus Knowledge:&lt;br /&gt;
Understanding of Apache/nginx configuration&lt;br /&gt;
High availability configuration for CMS driven websites&lt;br /&gt;
MySQL skills&lt;br /&gt;
Mobile Web App Development (Apple or Android) &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competitive pay and ability to work on fantastic clients in a laid back fun environment. The experience of working directly with friendly and supportive clients. Some of our past and current clients include sba.gov, sprint.com, large associations with major offices in DC area (can&#039;t mention them by name), startups, small business and lots of creative companies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are working on leading edge technology with clients that are pushing the envelope; you will be expected to work with our developers hand in hand on these projects. It&#039;s like getting paid to gain skills that are in very high demand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course we offer competitive compensation, full health care plan and profit sharing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Promet Source is an Open Source Web and Mobile web application development company. Promet has been building open source websites since 2003. We are a very entrepreneurial company which seeks to continually redevelop its skill set. We are a flat organization which means everyone has a say and we encourage everyone to develop their interest. We love to work on social aspects of the web and mobile apps. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please email resumes to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:jobs2@promethost.com&quot;&gt;jobs2@promethost.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2011 17:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>theabrown</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">453 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Director, Cloud Service Operations</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/director-cloud-service-operations</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acquia&#039;s CloudOps team manages, monitors, and maintains thousands of server instances delivering billions of requests monthly for some of the world&#039;s largest Drupal-powered web sites. CloudOps is a 24x7 devops team powered by great tools and teamwork. We delight customers with on-demand scalability, top performance, and a time-saving user experience.&lt;br /&gt;
We are looking for a smart, execution-focused leader to grow and manage our outstanding team of systems engineers and admins. Director, CloudOps is highly visible as Cloud services are critical to Acquia&#039;s success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful candidates will&lt;br /&gt;
•	Communicate effectively with customers, employees, peers, and leadership&lt;br /&gt;
•	Assess and resolve complex issues, quickly, with incomplete information&lt;br /&gt;
•	Hire smart, passionate, and productive employees&lt;br /&gt;
•	Possess deep knowledge of internet and server technologies&lt;br /&gt;
•	Measurably improve our service&#039;s reliability, scalability, manageability, and security&lt;br /&gt;
•	Drive simple, efficient processes and the tools that support them&lt;br /&gt;
•	Understand our customers and our business to ensure the success of both&lt;br /&gt;
•	Respond well under pressure&lt;br /&gt;
•	Manage 24x7 support rotations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit resume to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 20:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">448 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Developer/Web Engineer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/achieve-internet/drupal-developerweb-engineer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/achieve-internet&quot;&gt;Achieve Internet&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Achieve Internet is the premier provider in Enterprise Drupal Architecture, integration and module customization. Our expertise in scalability of high traffic websites allows us the ability to provide enterprise level solutions for the most demanding environments. We have built some of the most dynamic and expansive Drupal websites on the market today. Achieve&#039;s success is based on our Common Vision. Our team consists of industry leaders who not only understand our mission, but consistently execute upon it. We carefully choose each member of our team based on both their passion for staying at the forefront of technology and driving customer success. Please visit our website &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.achieveinternet.com&quot; title=&quot;www.achieveinternet.com&quot;&gt;www.achieveinternet.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information about us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Achieve&#039;s Career Priorities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal Advancement. Our engineers are among the best in the Drupal world. Management invests extensively in the training and support of our engineers because we believe in our team. As you succeed we succeed and above all, our clients succeed with solutions that enable them to execute upon their business strategies. We will carefully map out your career path and give you the tools to be successful. Expect to be part of a challenging, cutting edge, technological environment that strives to provide the most effective software solutions for today and tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teamwork. A constant interchange of ideas exists between Achieve Internet&#039;s team members, creating a technological &quot;think tank.&quot; Each individual brings unique perspectives and skill sets to the company. The personal investment team members apply to projects proves their craft, time and time again. Their commitment and dedication to Achieve Internet&#039;s customers enable us to continually develop as a business team while delivering high-quality software solutions to our customers. If you are as business savvy as you are technologically smart, we&#039;re interested in speaking with you. Achieve Internet is a dynamic and exciting place to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking to add an experienced software developer to fill our Senior Drupal  Engineer role. The ideal candidate will have 5+ years of experience working with PHP and MySQLweb related code. Our lead developers collaborate with our Project Management team to build requirements documents, estimates and specs for client projects. Ability to mentor developers, communicate with the client, diagnose and fix issues as well as keep projects on time is what we are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position is located in our office in San Diego. Achieve Internet offers a competitive salary, health care benefits, life insurance &amp;amp; paid vacation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Desired skills:&lt;br /&gt;
* PHP and MySQL experience required (preferably PHP 5 and MySQL 5)&lt;br /&gt;
* Extensive experience with Drupal&lt;br /&gt;
* Experience leading a development team&lt;br /&gt;
* Experience creating client documentation (requirements, scope of work, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;
* Experience working in Agile development environment&lt;br /&gt;
* Superior written and verbal communication&lt;br /&gt;
* Proven client relations skills a must&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br /&gt;
* Lead the team through analysis and design to development, test and delivery&lt;br /&gt;
* Leads review of analysis, designs and code to ensure requirements are met&lt;br /&gt;
* Leads the team to finish a project 100% to customer satisfaction&lt;br /&gt;
* Custom PHP/MySQL coding (e.g., Drupal modules and custom db queries)&lt;br /&gt;
* Website architecture planning&lt;br /&gt;
* Work with Project Manager to create Scope of Work, requirements analysis, etc. for client projects by providing technical   details and estimates.&lt;br /&gt;
* Installation and configuration of Drupal-powered websites&lt;br /&gt;
* Client contact throughout development process &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We require all development applicants to pass a short programming test before the interview process begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please visit our career page at &lt;a href=&quot;http://achieveinternet.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;http://achieveinternet.com/careers&quot;&gt;http://achieveinternet.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 22:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>rmontero</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">442 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Internet Cloud Systems Engineer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/internet-cloud-systems-engineer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does cloud technology get your creative mind racing? Do you love building and debugging open-source, LAMP-stack architectures? Do you want to manage the largest Drupal-based sites on the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acquia is looking for expert, passionate systems engineers and systems administrators to help us grow our second-to-none Managed Cloud and Dev Cloud Drupal hosting services. We manage over 2,000 servers delivering some of the world&#039;s most popular Drupal web sites. Our easy-to-use Drupal Gardens service is running over 40,000 web sites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Constantly improve the performance and reliability of our hosting platforms&lt;br /&gt;
    Debug intriguing LAMP stack problems&lt;br /&gt;
    Work closely with customer support and engineering to deliver second-to-none SaaS and PaaS services&lt;br /&gt;
    Maintain and enhance cloud management and monitoring tools&lt;br /&gt;
    Participate in an on-call, operations support rotation&lt;br /&gt;
    Capacity planning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What We&#039;re Looking For&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Passion for web site configuration, tuning and troubleshooting&lt;br /&gt;
    Deep, working knowledge of web, database, and OS server configuration (Linux, Apache, and MySQL preferred platforms)&lt;br /&gt;
    Holistic understanding of the Internet and hosting from the network layer up through the application layer.&lt;br /&gt;
    Experience in a 24x7 hosting environment&lt;br /&gt;
    Experience with monitoring tools, scripting, and internet security&lt;br /&gt;
    3 to 10 years of related experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extra Credit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Cloud hosting experience (e.g., Amazon Web Services, Eucalyptus)&lt;br /&gt;
    Monitoring tools (e.g., Nagios, Cacti, Ganglia, Splunk, BMC, OpenView)&lt;br /&gt;
    Configuration management (e.g., Puppet, Chef, Subversion, Git)&lt;br /&gt;
    Scripting experience with PHP, Perl, or Ruby&lt;br /&gt;
    Web security (e.g., IDS systems, DOS prevention)&lt;br /&gt;
    Scalable hosting cluster experience (e.g., nginx, Varnish, GlusterFS, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;
    Drupal experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apply here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 18:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">440 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Cloud/LAMP Infrastructure Developer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/cloudlamp-infrastructure-developer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Does cloud technology get your creative mind racing? Do you like creating tools that manage complex hosting environments? ... solving tough architecture problems? ... developing software to control 100s of servers?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an exceptional web infrastructure software engineer who desires to deliver world-class performance and powerful developer-centric workflows. At Acquia, we are obsessive about our customers&#039; uptime and scalability and are looking for same. We manage over 600 server instances delivering some of the world&#039;s most popular Drupal sites on our Dev Cloud and Managed Cloud platforms. Our easy-to-use Drupal Gardens service is running over 40,000 web sites!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Design and develop tools that automatically deploy, maintain, and monitor LAMP-based hosting environments&lt;br /&gt;
    Research, specify, and test hosting architectures leveraging your web, database, and OS knowledge&lt;br /&gt;
    Debug tough web service production issues (tier 4 support)&lt;br /&gt;
    Share your expertise with customers, partners, and the Drupal community via blogs, papers, talks, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What We&#039;re Looking For&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Strong software development and technical leadership skills&lt;br /&gt;
    Passion for web site configuration, tuning and troubleshooting&lt;br /&gt;
    Deep, working knowledge of Linux, Apache, and MySQL&lt;br /&gt;
    Holistic understanding of the Internet and hosting from the network layer up through the application layer.&lt;br /&gt;
    3 to 12 years of related experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extra Credit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Languages: Ruby, PHP&lt;br /&gt;
    Cloud hosting experience (e.g., Amazon Web Services, VMWare, Eucalyptus)&lt;br /&gt;
    Web Development (e.g., Drupal, CSS, JSON, Jquery)&lt;br /&gt;
    Configuration management (e.g., Puppet, Chef, Subversion, Git)&lt;br /&gt;
    Web security (e.g., IDS systems, DOS prevention)&lt;br /&gt;
    Networking (e.g., TCP/IP, load balancing, clustering)&lt;br /&gt;
    Linux packages (e.g., Debian or RPM packages)&lt;br /&gt;
    Excellent organizational and communication skills, both verbal and written&lt;br /&gt;
    BS in Computer Science or a related field or equivalent experience&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position is available at Acquia’s main office in Burlington, MA just north of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit resume: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 18:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">439 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Senior Director of Cloud Product Marketing</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/senior-director-cloud-product-marketing</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Sr. Director of Cloud Product Marketing at Acquia is the face of the products to the market. This person will evangelize Acquia&#039;s cloud products in the form of speaking engagements, webinars, customer briefings and other public facing activities. To support these efforts, the Director will lead the development of market positioning, messaging, web content, and collateral for multiple Acquia products, as well as work closely with product owners to determine market requirements and strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an experienced product marketing professional to join our Marketing team to support our Cloud hosting and applications products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    Development of messaging and positioning for Acquia products, working closely with R&amp;amp;D to translate product capabilities into features and benefits for customers.&lt;br /&gt;
    Work closely with Product Owner to perform market research to evaluate potential requirements and shape future product direction.&lt;br /&gt;
    Create and deliver customer-facing presentations, including in-person speaking engagements and live webinars.&lt;br /&gt;
    Engage with industry analysts to educate them on Acquia products and research market trends to drive product direction.&lt;br /&gt;
    Develop go-to-market programs in conjunction with Marketing Programs team to generate leads and meet quarterly objectives. Create all web content, product videos, product collateral and sales training materials required in execution of GTM programs.&lt;br /&gt;
    Plan, develop and deliver product webinars. Responsibilities include planning and scheduling of webinars to match quarterly marketing objectives, writing webinar abstracts, creating and delivering webinar presentations.&lt;br /&gt;
    Work closely with content and public relations team to develop and execute content strategies to generate media / blogger interest in Acquia products. Act as spokesperson for products and generate byline content for media distribution.&lt;br /&gt;
    Develop case studies and customer briefs – working with sales and customers to coordinate customer case studies.&lt;br /&gt;
    Train the Acquia sales team on product capabilities, positioning in the market versus competitors and effective selling strategies.&lt;br /&gt;
    Work with Acquia partners to plan product-specific GTM activities with key partners including whitepapers, case studies, trade shows, advertising, and joint marketing/ selling strategies.&lt;br /&gt;
    Produce monthly and quarterly reporting of marketing metrics&lt;br /&gt;
    Travel required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qualifications&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    3-5 years experience in a product marketing / product management role&lt;br /&gt;
    Specific experience in the hosting market space is a plus. Candidate must understand hosting and cloud landscape, including IaaS, PaaS and SaaS markets.&lt;br /&gt;
    Public speaking experience is a must, at both in-person events, including conferences, tradeshows, and developer camps, and online events, specifically webinars and virtual conferences.&lt;br /&gt;
    Experience managing marketing activities across multiple software products.&lt;br /&gt;
    Demonstrated track record developing messaging and positioning for web software products, including market research and all collateral development.&lt;br /&gt;
    Excellent organizational skills, ability to multi-task, software knowledge, and experience in marketing enterprise level software are all requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&#039;s it like to work at Acquia?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As an incredibly fast growing company, at Acquia we are always looking for the best of the best. We look for people that are passionate, intelligent, full of integrity, and are super stars (or future super stars!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are an open source company that values community, free speech (and beer) and technical software innovation that you can&#039;t find in other companies. We&#039;re a fast growing, hot startup company that wants to help make Drupal the world dominant Web platform. Join us as we help change the way people think about the Web and Social Software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit resume: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 18:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">438 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Client Advisor, Drupal Gardens</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/client-advisor-drupal-gardens</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The economy is fueling open-source adoption and Drupal is taking off. If you are interested in getting involved in the next big thing, look at Acquia, the leading provider of commercial support for Drupal. &quot;Home&quot; of Drupal creator Dries Buytaert, we are hiring both full-time and part-time help!&lt;br /&gt;
Acquia is a springboard for motivated young professionals to get their foot in the door of one of the hottest tech startups. We are seeking people who are passionate about the web and site development, including cross-browser, cross-platform website building experience. We need smart, focused and determined individuals who have a proven ability to listen, read between the lines, and diagnose and solve problems efficiently.&lt;br /&gt;
We’re like the Genius Bar, only with a lot less attitude.&lt;br /&gt;
Eager learners desiring to add Drupal to their tech toolbox, step right up to the front of the line and come on board. Recent graduates, career changers, and those coming from non-traditional backgrounds that can hit home runs are encouraged to apply.&lt;br /&gt;
Positions are available locally in Boston, Portland OR, and Oxford UK. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br /&gt;
You will join a dedicated team of remote consultants; helping Drupal Gardens users all over the world build killer web experiences with this amazing SaaS tool. As part of that team, you will work directly with our customers helping them resolve issues and providing coaching on CSS and Drupal. You will develop and maintain excellent relationships with our customers.&lt;br /&gt;
You will also have a chance to work with some of the web’s sharpest technical minds, and contribute to making Acquia and Drupal even more awesome. In this entry-level position, you will have an opportunity to learn constantly and will be at the start of an open-ended career at Acquia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br /&gt;
•	Passion for the web, open source, and for helping us build a hot and growing start-up&lt;br /&gt;
•	Excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br /&gt;
•	Proficient in HTML, CSS, and other Web 2.0/3.0 technologies&lt;br /&gt;
•	Strong knowledge of Drupal a plus&lt;br /&gt;
•	Bachelor&#039;s or master&#039;s degree in Computer Science or related discipline preferred&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summer 2010 internships also available; please indicate interest with your resume submission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Submit resume: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 18:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">437 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Client Advisor</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/acquia/client-advisor</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/acquia&quot;&gt;Acquia&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Acquia is looking for Drupal experts and technical advisors to join our customer advisory team to help us provide exceptional service to our growing customer base, from Fortune 500 clients to government agencies. We need smart, focused and determined individuals who have a proven ability to listen, read between the lines, and diagnose and solve problems efficiently. You get to advise Acquia customers on how to get the most from Drupal and guide them through issues from site launches to &quot;there&#039;s a module for that&quot; scenarios. We’re like the Genius Bar, only with a lot less attitude. :)&lt;br /&gt;
Positions are available locally in Boston, Portland OR, and London UK. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;br /&gt;
You will join a dedicated team of remote consultants; helping customers all over the globe overcome obstacles related to their websites. As part of that team, you will work directly with our customers and partners to resolve issues, develop and maintain excellent customer relationships, work with Acquia’s team of top Drupalists to consult or resolve issues, and contribute to making Acquia and Drupal even more awesome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qualifications:&lt;br /&gt;
•	Passion for the web, open-source development, and for helping us build a hot and growing start-up&lt;br /&gt;
•	Deep knowledge of Drupal&lt;br /&gt;
•	A compulsion for creating order out of chaos, and a penchant for turning over all the rocks and resolving issues thoroughly&lt;br /&gt;
•	Deep understanding of LAMP or IIS/SQL, network protocol layers, security layers and domain models&lt;br /&gt;
•	Aptitude for building, configuring, and troubleshooting a variety of Drupal site recipes (complex sites, multimedia, social networking, brochure sites, etc.)&lt;br /&gt;
•	Excellent interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br /&gt;
•	Bachelor&#039;s or Master&#039;s degree in computer science or related discipline preferred&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summer 2010 internships also available; please indicate interest with your resume submission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apply Here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.acquia.com/careers&quot; title=&quot;www.acquia.com/careers&quot;&gt;www.acquia.com/careers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nicole.pare</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">436 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Rideshare for soniasbs</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/435</link>
 <description>&lt;p&gt;I need a ride from Palo Alto on Saturday. I can drive Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/435#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://badcamp2011.dev/taxonomy/term/9">I could drive or ride</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 15:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>soniasbs</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">435 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Rideshare for mmdavis</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/434</link>
 <description>&lt;h3 class=&quot;location-locations-header&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location-locations-wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location vcard&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;adr&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;fn&quot;&gt;Woodland, CA&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;country-name&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;map-link&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;location map-link&quot;&gt;See map: &lt;a href=&quot;http://maps.google.com?q=%2C+%2C+%2C+%2C+us&quot;&gt;Google Maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&#039;m planning on driving to and from Friday and Sunday. Will have room for one, possibly three.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/434#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://badcamp2011.dev/taxonomy/term/8">Offering a seat</category>
 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>mmdavis</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">434 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Developer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/ninjitsu-web-development/drupal-developer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/ninjitsu-web-development&quot;&gt;Ninjitsu Web Development&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether your new to Drupal, or a certified Rockstar, let&#039;s talk.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 17:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>matt2000</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">433 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Drupal Developer</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/program/job-fair/exaltation-larks/drupal-developer</link>
 <description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field-type-nodereference field-field-job-company&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;field-items&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;field-item odd&quot;&gt;
                      &lt;div class=&quot;field-label-inline-first&quot;&gt;
              Company:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;a href=&quot;/sponsors/exaltation-larks&quot;&gt;Exaltation of Larks&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exaltation of Larks has an immediate opening for a contract Drupal developer for 10-20+ hours per week. We&#039;re a bicoastal firm that likes to do things that have never been done before and we&#039;re growing. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(You can read more about what we do at our website: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.larks.la&quot; title=&quot;http://www.larks.la&quot;&gt;http://www.larks.la&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&#039;re looking for a developer with excellent knowledge of the Drupal API and Drupal processes. We need someone who has good communication skills, a sense of humor, and a desire to be part of a remote and occasionally local team. (Most of our team is in the Los Angeles and Boston areas, with others geographically scattered. We occasionally like to get together to work or play.) Be prepared to AIM, Jabber and Skype. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our current team is primarily using OS X and then Linux, with a sprinkle of Windows machines. Windows developers are welcomed, but might need an orientation to get up to speed on our sync and deployment methods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not require that you sit up straight, eat all your vegetables or wake up early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out our jobs page at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.larks.la/jobs&quot; title=&quot;http://www.larks.la/jobs&quot;&gt;http://www.larks.la/jobs&lt;/a&gt;, email us at jobs [at] larks [dot] la or contact us at our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.larks.la/contact&quot;&gt;contact page&lt;/a&gt; with your contact information and anything else that you’d like us to know. Be sure to include your hourly rate, references and time zone. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 07:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>nodiac</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">432 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Rideshare for gowri</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/431</link>
 <description>&lt;h3 class=&quot;location-locations-header&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location-locations-wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location vcard&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;adr&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;fn&quot;&gt;Vallejo&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;street-address&quot;&gt;Columbus Parkway very close Interstate 80&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;country-name&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;geo&quot;&gt;&lt;abbr class=&quot;latitude&quot; title=&quot;38.059337&quot;&gt;38° 3&#039; 33.6132&quot; N&lt;/abbr&gt;, &lt;abbr class=&quot;longitude&quot; title=&quot;-122.244873&quot;&gt;122° 14&#039; 41.5428&quot; W&lt;/abbr&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;map-link&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;location map-link&quot;&gt;See map: &lt;a href=&quot;http://maps.google.com?q=38.059337+-122.244873+%28Columbus+Parkway%2C+%2C+%2C+%2C+us%29&quot;&gt;Google Maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming from Vallejo, CA&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/431#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://badcamp2011.dev/taxonomy/term/9">I could drive or ride</category>
 <georss:point>38.059337 -122.244873</georss:point>
 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 04:58:48 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>gowri</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">431 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Rideshare for mototribe</title>
 <link>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/430</link>
 <description>&lt;h3 class=&quot;location-locations-header&quot;&gt;Location&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location-locations-wrapper&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;location vcard&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;adr&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;fn&quot;&gt;Castro Valley&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;street-address&quot;&gt;Lamar Loop&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;country-name&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;map-link&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;location map-link&quot;&gt;See map: &lt;a href=&quot;http://maps.google.com?q=Lamar+Loop%2C+%2C+%2C+%2C+us&quot;&gt;Google Maps&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live in Castro Valley and ride my motorcycle to Badcamp. I have an extra motorcycle and a guest room to stay - hit me up if you have a motorcycle license and need a room to crash&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
 <comments>http://badcamp2011.dev/node/430#comments</comments>
 <category domain="http://badcamp2011.dev/taxonomy/term/9">I could drive or ride</category>
 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2011 04:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
 <dc:creator>mototribe</dc:creator>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">430 at http://badcamp2011.dev</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
